=Love Lurking=
=الحب الكامن=
=Episode 9=
=الحلقة 9=
Oh, no!
أوه لا!
Boss, are you okay?
يا رئيس، هل أنت بخير؟
Kill them!
اقتلوهم!
I killed someone.
لقد قتلت شخصا ما.
It's okay now.
لا بأس الآن.
Don't be afraid.
لا تخف.
Gu Nian,
قو نيان,
get out of here.
اخرج من هنا.
Forget everything here.
انسى كل شيء هنا.
Start your life over.
أبدأ حياتك من جديد.
Can't we leave together?
ألا يمكننا أن نغادر معًا؟
No.
لا.
Neither of you can leave here alive today.
لا يستطيع أي منكما مغادرة هذا المكان حيًا اليوم.
(Half a year later)
(بعد نصف عام)
Nian.
لنا.
Aside from the nightmares,
بصرف النظر عن الكوابيس،
your recovery has been good.
لقد كان تعافيك جيدا.
But whenever I pick up a scalpel now,
ولكن كلما التقطت مشرطًا الآن،
I relive that moment I fired the gun.
أستعيد تلك اللحظة التي أطلقت فيها النار.
It's a residual effect of your PTSD.
إنه التأثير المتبقي لاضطراب ما بعد الصدمة.
Full recovery will take time.
سوف يستغرق التعافي الكامل بعض الوقت.
The drug dealers you encountered six months ago are all dead.
تجار المخدرات الذين واجهتهم قبل ستة أشهر جميعهم ماتوا.
So you don't have to fear anymore.
لذلك لا داعي للخوف بعد الآن.
Nian,
لنا،
let's have dinner together tonight.
دعونا نتناول العشاء معًا الليلة.
Probably not.
ربما لا.
The dean wants to talk about my mother with me.
يريد العميد أن يتحدث معي عن والدتي.
I'm off.
انا ذاهب.
Wait.
انتظر.
You said that medication caused hallucinations.
قلت أن الدواء يسبب الهلوسة.
I've changed your prescription.
لقد غيرت الوصفة الطبية الخاصة بك.
It should work better.
ينبغي أن يعمل بشكل أفضل.
Thanks, Senior.
شكرا لك يا كبير السن.
He is your target tonight.
إنه هدفك الليلة.
The dean of Grace Hospital.
عميد مستشفى جريس.
The dean isn't taking calls.
العميد لا يستقبل المكالمات.
Is he in his office?
هل هو في مكتبه؟
Alright. I'm heading over now.
حسنًا، سأذهب الآن.
Sorry.
آسف.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Am I hallucinating again?
هل أنا أتوهم مرة أخرى؟
Dean, are you inside?
دين، هل أنت بالداخل؟
It's Nian.
إنه نيان.
Help.
يساعد.
Dean, wake up!
دين، استيقظ!
Stop.
قف.
Or I'll kill you.
أو سأقتلك.
Dean, I have a document requiring your signature.
عميد، لدي وثيقة تتطلب توقيعك.
Nian, you're awake.
نيان، أنت مستيقظ.
The dean? Where's the dean?
العميد؟ أين العميد؟
We tried resuscitating him.
لقد حاولنا إنعاشه.
But he still passed from a heart attack.
ولكنه توفي بسبب نوبة قلبية.
A heart attack?
نوبة قلبية؟
No. I saw the killer.
لا، لقد رأيت القاتل.
The dean was murdered.
تم اغتيال العميد.
Miss Gu,
السيدة جو،
are you sure you witnessed someone killed the dean?
هل أنت متأكد أنك شهدت شخصًا يقتل العميد؟
I didn't see him commit the murder.
لم أرى أنه يرتكب جريمة القتل.
But he was at the scene.
ولكنه كان في مكان الحادث.
The surveillance?
المراقبة؟
We checked the footage.
لقد قمنا بفحص اللقطات.
No one was seen entering or leaving the dean's office.
ولم يشاهد أحد يدخل أو يخرج من مكتب العميد.
Miss Gu, if there truly is a killer,
آنسة جو، إذا كان هناك قاتل حقًا،
you might be in danger.
ربما تكون في خطر.
Please be careful.
يرجى توخي الحذر.
Stop. Or I'll kill you.
توقف وإلا سأقتلك.
(Why did that man sound so much like him?)
(لماذا كان صوت هذا الرجل يشبه صوته إلى هذا الحد؟)
If I had gone to see the dean earlier that day,
لو ذهبت لرؤية العميد في وقت سابق من ذلك اليوم،
he might not have been killed.
ربما لم يكن قد قُتل.
Maybe there was no killer at all.
ربما لم يكن هناك قاتل على الإطلاق.
It could just be hallucinations from your medication.
ربما تكون مجرد هلوسات بسبب دوائك.
Even you don't believe me?
حتى أنت لا تصدقني؟
Nian, that's not what I meant.
نيان، هذا ليس ما قصدته.
I heard the dean was murdered.
سمعت أن العميد تم اغتياله.
Could it be that the dean offended someone powerful
هل يمكن أن يكون العميد قد أساء إلى شخص قوي؟
like former Dean Gu?
مثل العميد السابق جو؟
Didn't Dean Gu kill herself over bribery charges?
ألم تنتحر العميد جو بسبب اتهامات الرشوة؟
Who knows?
من يعلم؟
Her daughter claimed there was a killer.
وزعمت ابنتها أن هناك قاتلًا.
It seems this time,
يبدو أن هذه المرة،
Dr. Gu says there's a killer too.
يقول الدكتور جو أن هناك قاتلًا أيضًا.
But they say she's hallucinating.
لكنهم يقولون أنها تعاني من الهلوسة.
So her testimony isn't credible.
لذلك شهادتها ليست ذات مصداقية.
Don't mind what they say.
لا تهتم بما يقولون.
By the way, I retrieved your phone.
بالمناسبة، لقد استعدت هاتفك.
(This isn't my phone.)
(هذا ليس هاتفي.)
Dean?
عميد؟
What's wrong, Dean?
ما الأمر يا دين؟
This is the dean's phone.
هذا هو هاتف العميد.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
(They must've returned the wrong phone.)
(لا بد أنهم أعادوا الهاتف الخطأ.)
The dean isn't taking calls.
العميد لا يستقبل المكالمات.
Alright. I'm heading over now.
حسنًا، سأذهب الآن.
(The dean's line was busy the entire time.)
(كان خط العميد مشغولاً طوال الوقت.)
(He was indeed on a call before the accident.)
(لقد كان في مكالمة بالفعل قبل الحادث.)
The dean refused to collaborate with the Wei Group.
رفض العميد التعاون مع مجموعة وي.
Could he have offended the Wei family's new head?
هل من الممكن أن يكون قد أساء إلى رئيس عائلة وي الجديد؟
What's his name?
ما اسمه؟
Song Qian?
سونغ تشيان؟
It's Song Qian, I think.
إنها سونغ تشيان، على ما أعتقد.
I heard he's ruthless and cruel.
سمعت أنه قاسي و عديم الرحمة.
He killed many people.
لقد قتل العديد من الناس.
Nian, what are you doing?
نيان ماذا تفعل؟
♪What is secretly stirring♪
♪ما الذي يتحرك سرا♪
♪From your mouth, I find it hard to describe♪
♪من فمك، أجد صعوبة في وصفه♪
♪What praises can disappear in just a second♪
♪ما هي الثناءات التي يمكن أن تختفي في ثانية واحدة♪
♪Vanishing without a trace♪
♪الاختفاء دون أثر♪
♪Waving hands to break free from the splendid cage♪
♪تلويح الأيدي للتحرر من القفص الرائع♪
♪Words against the heart, a pain slashes through the sky♪
♪كلمات ضد القلب، ألم يشق السماء♪
♪Floating into the endless night sky, the wind fierce and strong♪
♪تطفو في سماء الليل اللامتناهية، والرياح شرسة وقوية♪
♪Who is reckless, continuing to lose control, with impunity♪
♪من هو المتهور، الذي يستمر في فقدان السيطرة، مع الإفلات من العقاب♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪
♪Cannot see who is pulling the strings behind♪
♪لا أستطيع أن أرى من يسحب الخيوط من الخلف♪
♪The wound still aches, and the memory is not yet over♪
♪الجرح لا يزال يؤلمني، والذكرى لم تنته بعد♪
♪There are two endings, whether you understand or not♪
♪هناك نهايتان، سواء فهمت أم لا♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪
♪Cannot see who is tracking from behind♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية من يتتبعني من الخلف♪
♪The heart still beats, total blood-red before my eyes♪
♪لا يزال القلب ينبض، أحمر اللون كالدم أمام عيني♪
♪Only one ending remains, whether it helps or not♪
♪تبقى نهاية واحدة فقط، سواء كانت مفيدة أم لا♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪